[{"question":"<p><strong>The current life expectancy in Nigeria is<\/strong><\/p>","options":["55","47","39","45"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Yumu and Zabara are ethnic groups in&nbsp;<\/strong><\/p>","options":["Kebbi State","Benue State","Niger state","Kano state"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Mr Dele Giwa was killed through a letter bomb on<\/strong><\/p>","options":["October 19, 1986","September 17, 1987","October 19, 1986","September 17, 1986"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>The following are spices except<\/strong><br \/><br \/><\/p>","options":["Rye","Saffron","Ginger","Cloves"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Desmond Tutu was awarded the Nobel Peace Prize in<\/strong><\/p>","options":["1983","1987","2001","1984"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Victoria is the capital city of<\/strong><\/p>","options":["Somalia","Morocco","Seychelles","Burundi"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>The Director-General of the Nigerian Institute of Advanced Legal Studies is<\/strong><\/p>","options":["Prof. Pat Utomi","Prof. Epiphany Azinge","Justice Nikki Tobi","Prof. (Mrs) Bolanle Awe"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Centre of Unity is to Abuja as State of Hospitality is to<\/strong><\/p>","options":["Rivers","Cross River","Sokoto","Nassarawa"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>The capital of Uruguay is<\/strong><br \/><strong>&nbsp;<\/strong><\/p>","options":["Bangkok","Montevideo","Bern","Manila"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>The Governor of Anambra State is<\/strong><\/p>","options":["Mr. Peter Obi","Owelle Rochas Okorocha","Peter Odili","Chris Ngige"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>____ was the Chief Justice of Nigeria between 1995 and 2006<\/strong><br \/><br \/><\/p>","options":["Justice Idris Lagbo Kutigi","Justice Mohammad Lawal Uwais","Justice George Sodeinde Sowemimo","Justice Salihu Modibo Alfa Belgore"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>The current Secretary-General of the United Nations is from<\/strong><\/p>","options":["United Kingdom","South Korea","Ghana","South Africa"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>The capital of Iran is<\/strong><\/p>","options":["Iranian","Dublin","Baghdad","Teheran"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>The full meaning of UEFA is<\/strong><br \/><br \/><\/p>","options":["Union of European Federation Associations","United European Football Associations","Union of European Football Associations","United English Football Associations"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Nelson Mandela was awarded the Nobel Peace Prize in<\/strong><\/p>","options":["1992","1993","1994","1995"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Ibeno Beach is in<\/strong><\/p>","options":["Lagos State","Cross River State","Akwa Ibom State","Taraba State"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>The June 12 Presidential election was annulled by President Ibrahim Babangida on<\/strong><\/p>","options":["June 12 1993","June 14 1993","June 18 1993","June 23 1993"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Gombe State belongs to the ____ geo-political zone in Nigeria<\/strong><\/p>","options":["South East","South West","North Central","North Eest"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>The full meaning of OECD is<\/strong><br \/><br \/><\/p>","options":["Organization for Economic Co-operation and Development","Organization of Economic Co-operation and Development","Organization of Economic Community and Development\u00a0","Organization for Economic Community and Development"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Paparada Square is in<\/strong><\/p>","options":["Ilorin","Lokoja","Kaduna","Lagos"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>The former Eastern Region was proclaimed a sovereign nation, Biafra by Odumegu Ojukwu on<\/strong><\/p>","options":["May 30, 1967","June 15, 1966","April 6, 1968","January 10, 1965"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>The Kruger National Park is in<\/strong><\/p>","options":["South Africa","Tunisia","Cameroon","Poland"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>The official residence of the Secretary-General of the United Nations is in<\/strong><\/p>","options":["Washington D.C. United States","New York City, United States","Birmingham, United Kingdom","Atlanta Georgia, United States"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Dar es Salaam is the capital of<\/strong><br \/><br \/><br \/><\/p>","options":["Tunisia","Turkey","Zimbabwe","Tanzania"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Shanga and Kyenga are ethnic groups in<\/strong><\/p>","options":["Sokoto State","Bauchi State","Niger State","Kwara State"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>FESTAC started in<\/strong><\/p>","options":["October 1976","October 1978","November 1977","November 1978"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Which of these was never a Senate President in Nigeria?<\/strong><br \/><br \/><\/p>","options":["Iyocha Ayu","Chuba Okadigbo","Pius Anyim","Umaru Dikko"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>The United Nations Charter was formed on<\/strong><br \/><br \/><\/p>","options":["1 February 1946","26 June 1945","24 October 1945","15 March 1943"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Abayon, Adim and Adun are ethnic groups in<\/strong><\/p>","options":["Taraba State","Cross River State","Bauchi State","Adamawa State"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Barack Obama was awarded the Nobel Peace Prize in<\/strong><\/p>","options":["2000","2003","2007","2009"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>The capital of Greece is<\/strong><\/p>","options":["Greek","Athens","Rome","Jerusalem"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Assop Falls can be found in<\/strong><\/p>","options":["Plateau State","Kano State","Taraba State","Niger State"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>The Secretary-General of the United Nations between 1972 and 1981 was<\/strong><br \/><br \/><\/p>","options":["Javier Perez de Cuellar","Alger Hiss","Kofi Annan","Kurt Waldheim"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Ken Saro-Wiwa and eight others were executed in<\/strong><\/p>","options":["1994","1995","1996","1997"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Albert Lutuli was awarded the Nobel Peace Prize in<\/strong><\/p>","options":["1960","1970","1947","1909"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Ronald Reagan, the former US President, was a<\/strong><\/p>","options":["Democrat","Republican","Federalist","Democratic-Republican"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Gurara Falls can be located in<\/strong><\/p>","options":["Niger State","Imo State","Edo State","Adamawa State"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Obudu Cattle Ranch is in<\/strong><\/p>","options":["Rivers State","Cross River State","Bayelsa State","Delta State"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Alau Dam and Alan Lake are located in<\/strong><\/p>","options":["Calabar","Warri","Maiduguri","Ebonyi"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>The National Security Adviser is<\/strong><\/p>","options":["Gen. Andrew Owoeye Azazi (rtd)","Col. Sambo Dasuki","Gen. Aliyu Mohammed Gusau","Col. Kayode Are"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Maseru is the capital city of<\/strong><\/p>","options":["Mauritius","Rwanda","Lesotho","Tunisia"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>The Inspector-General of Police is<\/strong><br \/><br \/><br \/><br \/><\/p>","options":["Mr Iyami Aganike","Alhaji Mohammed Dahiru Abubakar","Mr Tafa Balogun","Mr Muhammed Katsina"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>The Minster of Health is<\/strong><\/p>","options":["Prof. Olikoye Ransome Kuti","Prof. C.O.Onyebuchi","Prof. Babatunde Osotimehin","Dr (Mrs) Grange Alice"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"}]